dailyprincetonian.com 2011-12-31

# Daily Princetonian Privacy Statement - The Daily Princetonian

#### Contents

  1. Information Collection & Use
    1. Registration
    2. Orders
    3. E-Mail Referrals
    4. Uses of Information
  2. Communications from the Site
    1. E-Prince
    2. Customer Service
  3. Information Sharing & Disclosure
    1. Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
    2. Personally Identifiable Information
    3. Agents
    4. Legal Disclaimer
  4. Choice & Opt-out
  5. Log Files
  6. Cookies
  7. Third Party Advertisers
  8. Links to Other Sites
  9. User Submitted Content
  10. Access to Personally Identifiable Information
  11. Security
  12. Changes to this Privacy Policy
  13. Contact Us

#### Information Collection & Use

##### Registration

To use this website, you should first complete the registration form and create a username and password. During registration you give contact information (such as name and e-mail address). We use this information to allow readers to subscribe to the online and print editions of The Daily Princetonian and comment on online stories.

You have the option to provide demographic information to us; we encourage you to submit this information so we can provide you a more personalized experience on our site.

The Daily Princetonian Publishing Company, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on www.dailyprincetonian.com and all affiliated sites and domains. The Daily Princetonian Publishing Company, Inc. collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our website.

##### Orders

If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, e-mail address and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

##### E-Mail this Story

If you choose to use our e-mail referral service to tell a friend about stories on our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and e-mail address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time e-mail providing a link to the article. The Daily Princetonian Publishing Company, Inc. stores this information only for the purposes of sending this one-time e-mail and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may [](mailto:web@dailyprincetonian.com%3E%20contact%20us%20%3C/a%3Eto%20request%20that%20we%20remove%20this%20information%20from%20our%20database.%3Cp%3E%3Ca%20name=)

##### Uses of Information

The Daily Princetonian Publishing Company, Inc. uses the personal information collected on www.dailyprincetonian.com  and affiliated sites for billing, user interactivity and tracking purposes. Billing information is collected for the purpose of allowing users to subscribe to online or print editions of The Daily Princetonian. The information of users who interact with the site by registering their account information, commenting on stories or in any other manner is recorded by this and affiliated websites for aggregate tracking and feedback. Aggregate information on pageviews, e-mailed stories and comments is tracked with no personally identifiable information. Comments on stories and other user feedback are recorded with the personally identifiable account information that users choose to provide, and users retain the option to comment or otherwise give feedback anonymously.

#### Communications from the Site

##### E-Prince

If you wish to subscribe to our E-Prince service, we will use your name and e-mail address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the Choice & Opt-out section.

##### Customer Service

Based on the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you an e-mail to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you via e-mail in response to your inquiries to provide the services you request and manage your account. 

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

##### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. We track aggregate pageviews and other web traffic metrics to share with our partners and advertisers.

We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

##### Personally Identifiable Information

We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties.

##### Agents

We conduct online payments using [Paypal](http://www.paypal.com/). The Daily Princetonian Publishing Company, Inc. bears no responsibility for the use by Paypal of information transferred in the course of making a purchase. We do not retain, share or store or use personally identifiable information from Paypal purchases.

##### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information when we believe that disclosure is required by law or court order or to protect our rights.

#### Choice & Opt-out

Users of our site are under no obligation to disclose any personal information, and any such information disclosed by account registration or otherwise is done on a voluntary basis by users.

If you no longer wish to receive our E-Prince or other services, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each service or communication or by contacting us at [ subscriptions@dailyprincetian.com ](mailto:subscriptions@dailyprincetian.com) or (609) 258-8110. 

#### Log Files

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

We use a third-party tracking services, Google Analytics and Statcounter, that track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate, including pageviews, visitor network and browser information, and trends in page and content use.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers.”

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by www.dailyprincetonian.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

#### Third Party Advertisers

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by Google Adsense, Tribalfusion, and Personforce our advertising partners. We share website usage information about users with reputable third parties, Google Adsense and Tribalfusion, for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site.

Google Adsense, Tribalfusion, and Personforce may use cookies and clear GIFs on this site, which allow them to recognize a user's cookie when a user visits this site. The information that Google Adsense and Tribalfusion collects and shares through this technology is not personally identifiable.

For more information about our third-party advertisers, or to learn more about the choices available to you regarding this anonymous information, see <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html>, <http://www.tribalfusion.com/TribalFusion/privacy.html>, or [http://www.personforce.com](http://www.personforce.com/).

#### Links to Other Sites

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by The Daily Princetonian Publishing Company, Inc. Please be aware that we, The Daily Princetonian Publishing Company, Inc, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website.

#### User Submitted Content

If you use the user comment or other user content submission feature on this or affiliated sites, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information and content (including but not limited to comments on stories and feedback) you choose to submit in these forums, and reserve the right to delete, modify, or preserve potentially for public view any content submitted by users as published, posted or otherwise submitted to this site or its affiliates. The final decisions regarding any treatment of user submitted content will be made by the Editor-in-Chief of The Daily Princetonian. Questions regarding user submitted content should be sent to one of the locations provided below.

#### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our services, you may correct, update or delete it by making the change on our registration page or by contacting us.

#### Security

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us.

#### Changes in this Privacy Statement

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here.

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us by e-mail at [web@dailyprincetonian.com](mailto:web@dailyprincetonian.com), by phone at (609) 258-3632, or by mail at the address:

The Daily Princetonian Web Office  
48 University Place  
Princeton, New Jersey 08540.

Last updated 2.22.2009
